Turning up emotional faders
Keep repeating self-hating phrases
This is biological stasis
My mood's shifting to manic places
Wish I laughed and kept the good friendships
Watch life, here I go again
I can't see me cry
Can't see me cry ever again
Can't see me cry
This is the end
My biggest enemy is me, pop a 911
My biggest enemy is me
Ever since day one
Pop a 911, then pop another one
Keep my dolls inside diamond boxes
Save them 'til I know I'm gon' drop this front
I've built around me, oasis
Paradise is in my hand
Holding on so tight to this status
It's not real but I'll try to grab it
Keep myself in beautiful places
Paradise is in my hands
I
can't see me cry
Can't see me cry ever again
I can't see me cry
Can't see me cry
This is the end
My biggest enemy is me, pop a 911
My biggest enemy is me
Ever since day one
Pop a 911 then pop another one
pop another one
I can't see me cry
Can't see me cry ever again
Can't see me cry
This is the end
My biggest enemy is me, pop a 911
My biggest enemy is me
Ever since day one
Pop a 911 then pop another one
Please patch the line
Need a 911, can you patch the line?